{
    "q1": {
        "id": "q1",
        "question": "Who is the leader of S.H.I.E.L.D.?",
        "answers": [
            "Nick Fury",
            "Tony Stark",
            "Bruce Banner",
            "Norman Osborn"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Nick Fury"
    },
    "q2": {
        "id": "q2",
        "question": "What was Pixar’s first movie?",
        "answers": [
            "Toy Story",
            "Finding Nemo",
            "A Bug's Life",
            "Cars"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Toy Story"
    },
    "q3": {
        "id": "q3",
        "question": "What is the name of the city that the Simpsons, the cartoon family, lives?",
        "answers": [
            "Springfield",
            "Des Moines",
            "Illinois",
            "Montgomery"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Springfield"
    },
    "q4": {
        "id": "q4",
        "question": "Which of the following is the highest-grossing video game franchise to date?",
        "answers": [
            "Call of Duty",
            "Pokemon",
            "Mario",
            "Tetris"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Tetris"
    },
    "q5": {
        "id": "q5",
        "question": "What is the name of Han Solo’s ship?",
        "answers": [
            "The Millenium Falcon",
            "Slave 1",
            "The Invisible Hand",
            "The Death Star"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Millenium Falcon"
    },
    "q6": {
        "id": "q6",
        "question": "Which wizard was portrayed by Christopher Lee in 'The Lord Of The Rings'?",
        "answers": [
            "Saruman",
            "Gandalf",
            "Radagast",
            "Merlin"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Saruman"
    },
    "q7": {
        "id": "q7",
        "question": "Which actor plays the role of Bucky Barnes in the Marvel Cinematic Universe?",
        "answers": [
            "Sebastian Stan",
            "Stellan Skarsgård",
            "John Slattery",
            "Jeff Goldblum"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sebastian Stan"
    },
    "q8": {
        "id": "q8",
        "question": "Which film contains the character Jules Winnfield?",
        "answers": [
          "A Streetcar Named Desire",
          "Grease",
          "Gangs of New York",
          "Pulp Fiction"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Pulp Fiction"
      },
      "q9": {
        "id": "q9",
        "question": "What video game character is the official mascot of Nintendo?",
        "answers": [
          "Sonic the Hedgehog",
          "Mario",
          "Spyro",
          "Crash Bandicoot"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Mario"
      },
      "q10": {
        "id": "q10",
        "question": "Which U.S. president was asked, but declined, to voice the in-game president character in Fallout 3?",
        "answers": [
          "Bill Clinton",
          "Barack Obama",
          "George W. Bush",
          "Donald Trump"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Bill Clinton"
      },
      "q11": {
        "id": "q11",
        "question": "What movie revolves around an alien being fostered by a Californian boy?",
        "answers": [
          "Blade Runner",
          "Breakfast Club",
          "E.T.",
          "The Martian"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "E.T."
      },
      "q12": {
        "id": "q12",
        "question": "What are The Simpsons Halloween specials known as?",
        "answers": [
          "Spooky Springfield",
          "The Halloween Haunt",
          "Evergreen Menace",
          "Treehouse of Horror"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Treehouse of Horror"
      },
      "q13": {
        "id": "q13",
        "question": "Which director directed 'Inglourious Basterds'?",
        "answers": [
          "Ridley Scott",
          "Spike Lee",
          "Oliver Stone",
          "Quentin Tarantino"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Quentin Tarantino"
      },
      "q14": {
        "id": "q14",
        "question": "Who is associated with the address '221B Baker Street, London'?",
        "answers": [
          "Harry Potter",
          "Charles Dickens",
          "Sherlock Holmes",
          "Thomas Hardy"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Sherlock Holmes"
      },
      "q15": {
        "id": "q15",
        "question": "What was the name of the talking car in the television show 'Knight Rider'?",
        "answers": [
          "HAL",
          "BENDER",
          "KITT",
          "JEEVES"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "KITT"
      }
}